Albert Torno Jr.



thedev.kenalbert@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/albert-t-98155165



09952277213



https://sk3ndi.github.io/portfolio project/

Summary

Got fundamental skills for HTML, CSS and Photoshop. Frequently using Wordpress to build websites. I've been exploring other platforms/tools to widen my knowledge and maintain best practices on web development.

Silent but easy to go with type of person. Believes that my experiences and skills are one of the factors in delivering awesome results for my clients.

Experience



Frontend & Wordpress | Shopify Developer

Freelance

May 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

- Design, build and maintain websites using WordPress. Edit and update existing shopify theme based on clients desired specifications.

Web & Wordpress Developer

R6

May 2022 - Sep 2023 (1 year 5 months)

- Design, build and maintain websites using WordPress. Turn FIGMA or Adobe XD designs into functional website.

Team Leader | Frontend & Wordpress Developer

Illumedia

Nov 2014 - Oct 2021 (7 years)

- Design, build and maintain websites using wordpress.
- Communicate with clients and update work tasks for my teammates.

Web Developer

HamakLabs

Jan 2014 - Aug 2014 (8 months)

Create and maintains web applications using MVC framework.

Education



Brokenshire College

2009 - 2013

Skills

PHP • Photoshop • HTML • CSS • SQL • Bootstrapping • Illustrator • Web Design • WordPress • Front-end Design